Thank you for watching.
How are you?
Hello! This time I'm joined by Rei Inoue of JuiceJuice and Colin Hashishita of Angulum.
This time, I'll be talking with Reie Inoue of JuiceJuice and Colin Hashishita of Angulum, so please bear with me until the end.
Project 2024 Summer All of Us: Vega and Altair is now underway.
This time, we have two names for you, Vega and Altair, the big triangles of summer.
I wonder what it's all about, it's all different. Yes, it is.
The songs are not slightly different, but 100 percent different, so rehearsals are very fresh.
It's been a while since I've been to a Halloween concert, so I'm looking forward to seeing the various interactions with the audience, and I know they're looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
It's the first time for us to see the new group, although there may be some people who are going to see the new group.
Has the current atmosphere of Angelem changed? Yes, I guess so.
I don't really feel any change in their mood or their performance, but when they sing, the ratio of members with higher voices has increased a little.
I guess it's because Mr. Sasaki was supporting me a lot downstairs.
I feel that the tone of your voice has risen dramatically since you have been supporting me so much.
I can feel it in unison, and the singing style has changed.
So when I see a new singer struggling with the new assignment...
Oh...
I felt that I didn't see it in many rehearsals, but when it comes to the performance, I'm sure the audience will feel it, so I hope both of them are good.
I'll do my best so that the audience will feel both sides are good.
Please take a look at the video.
Let's go!
Showcase Naraura Brawling Dance
Say I love it
Big things are relative, but the heart is relative
I'm in a hurry to jump on it, I want it to run away from me
Right?
Way way way way... I'm aiming for the other side.
What's your lucky number?
I'll catch you just the same All I want
Surprisingly high, that's the highest praise I'll ever get
I'm ready All night night night I'll never miss a moment
Kill my self-dream Get a chance
Baby spider
Come on come on now
Come on everybody
Get a chance
Baby spider
Come on, come on, come on, now!
Summer's airing
What you know?
I'm just trying to get a micro reaction in the comments section.
Simulations in your dreams, even if you don't have many.
I will gently entwine them with a red thread
Kuruna Love & Freedom
Hide it and run, run, run
Burn in the depths of my eyes
I want everything I want
I'll never give up
That's the only thing I won't lose
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, take your time
I'll let reason take its course
I can't help it.
I'm gonna do it with my voice
Baby restaurant
Even if they don't drop me
Working with Each Other
Oh Someday Someday Someday
That's the timing
So Wait Wait Wait
Just one more
Wa wa wa wa wa
Grab me by the forelock
I won't let go
Baby spider, you too
Baby spider. You too.
Hot hot hot
Someday I'll cry
All I want
In a piquant
The best you've ever seen
Words
I'm always ready
I never miss a moment
I'm sure you'll look away
Get a chance
Baby spider
Come on come on now
Come on everybody
Get a chance
Baby spider
Good work!
This is Rin Hashizoko from Juice Juice's Inomerite Angulum. I'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them in a quick tempo.
So, Lane, July marks the 5th anniversary since you joined Angsturm.
Let's see... When I was informed of my debut.
Six years ago now, Natsu Shogun was released for download. The first scene that comes to mind when I hear the name of this song is...
Um, me sitting in the cheering section What is the one thing you definitely want to do this summer?
Rin says she's been into traveling lately, so if you were to go on a trip next, where would it be?
Let's see... Fireworks display in Atami.
Wow, it's so nice!
Anna Kawamura-chan announced that she will graduate from the fall tour. Tell us what you want to do before she graduates.
Catch tuna together!
I've got too many things on my mind.
You were in the cheering section during Natsushogun? That's right. Cheering section. I was watching.
When I was a trainee... 6 years ago... the Hello Project concert in the summer of 2018...
I was sitting in the cheering section for the song "Natsu Shogun" as a trainee.
I was sitting in the cheering section for the song "Natsu Shogun" as a trainee, and I was so impressed that Mr. Takei, who was one of my seniors, came to sit next to me in the cheering section.
I thought they were really wonderful people, really wonderful people.
I loved it so much at the very end when they all gathered together and yelled "yay!
I just want to get my camera out and take a picture of it.
And it's so great to watch.
And you're looking right at the audience, right in front of them.
I'm thinking, "Isn't it great?
I want you to see it with your own eyes.
I think it's very good.
Also, you've been into traveling recently, haven't you?
Rin Kawahara and I went on a trip to Tochigi for the first time, and on the train on the way there, I realized how much I enjoyed the trip.
I looked up the schedule on my cell phone right then and there and thought, "Oh, there's going to be a fireworks display in Atami.
I wanted to go there, too.
I've always wanted to go to a summer festival every year.
I've always wanted to go to a summer festival every year, but I'm a bit of a lazy person.
What? Wait a minute. You don't want to schedule it?
That's right.
You've been thinking about going, but you just can't make plans.
Oh, I see.
So I'm hoping to go this year.
You seem like a pain in the ass.
Yes, I am.
Ha-ha-ha.
What do you mean?
Yes.
I'd like to wear a yukata... I think about it... but my mom says I shouldn't wear one because it's too thick.
It's interesting that you can imagine everything. I'd love for you to go. I'd love to go. Thank you.
And Inoue-san's question comes after the VTR. Sta.
Morning Musume。' 24Somewhat Sentimental Songs for a Sentimental Moment
August 14th On Sake
Morning Musume。' 24 The Strongest! August 14 Onsaker yo!
Tsubaki Factory New Single Seishun Exabyte August 28 Onsail
Tsubaki Factory New Single Baby Spider August 28th Onsweide
Hello! Project New Member Audition 2024
Celebrating its 27th year this year, Hello! Project is looking for new members!
Every member of Hello!
The important thing is to have the courage to take the first step!
We will do our best to support your first step!
This time, we will hold auditions in two categories
If you love singing, dancing, and Hello Project!
If you love singing, dancing, and Hello Project, you should audition in the Hello Project category.
And if you want to show off your skills and personality in addition to singing and dancing
Beyonds Potential Division!
If you want to make your dream come true with us at Hello! Project and make your dreams come true!
We are looking forward to hearing from you!
Next, I would like to ask Inoue-san a question.
Yay!
Okay, here we go.
Ms. Inoue celebrated her 23rd birthday two weeks ago.
What is your goal for your 23rd?
To take good care of myself.
Ms. Inoue, you bought a camera last year and have been taking a lot of pictures.
What is the subject you want to photograph most now?
Ami Tanimoto of Tsubaki Factory.
What fashion trend are you interested in this summer?
Happiness!
How do you keep your eyelashes long?
Don't blink your eyes!
It's been a month and a half since you became a sub-leader.
Someone who supports the group rather than leading it.
That's great!
There are many things that interest me.
Personally, I really like Inoue-san's photos of the members.
I like the side of the members that you take pictures of. I heard that you bought a camera last year and I've been watching your instagram and there is someone I would like to take pictures of.
So there is someone I would like to make my subject.
Why is that?
Well, we had been talking about having fun for a long time, but we haven't. We haven't really had any fun together.
Really, the two of us haven't played together once.
That's why I wanted to have fun with her. Ami-chan is really interesting in a way that you can't imagine from her picture.
That's right. So I'd like to do a shoot that gives a gap between the two of you, like a really beautiful work of art.
I would love to see that.
Let's do it!
How do you keep long eyelashes?
Yes!
I got a message from Moe-chan Shinkoku Ryu the other day.
He was talking about how Inoue-san's eyelashes are too beautiful in Angstrom.
How did she get them so long?
And why did I say I didn't draw her eyes?
I was so surprised, I didn't know it was possible to take off that many lashes in one day.
I thought it was really bad, so I thought it was really bad.
I want you to use eye drops when you have an itch, and I want the whole world to know about it.
Hello! We'll continue after this. Please join us.
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of the songs by Hello!
You, the viewers of "Hello! Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Rio Sakurai, will be presenting.
I often show my tongue.
This way.
That problem in front of you, that's not what you need to solve.
Take a deep breath slowly and let's talk about Halo! I will talk about Ste.
Take a bird's eye view! Morning Musume。 14's tomorrow will be made by you! The song is called "You will make the tomorrow of Morning Musume。
I performed this song for the first time at the first fall tour I participated in after my debut.
It was the fall tour of 2022, and I was still a new member, and my performance was not good at all.
I wasn't very good at singing or dancing, so there was a time when I didn't have much confidence in myself.
But when I heard this song on Settlement and listened to it for the first time, I was instantly impressed by the lyrics,
But when this song was in the set and I listened to it again for the first time, I was very impressed with the lyrics,
I was in the Settlement, and for the first time, I listened to this song with a new look at the lyrics,
I was in the Settlement at once,
Once you look at the problem in front of you like this...
I thought it would be best to look at my current situation from a bird's eye view, instead of trying so hard to memorize the words,
I was in a panic at the time, but listening to this song, I was able to calm down again.
Especially the use of the word "bird's eye view".
I don't often use the word "bird's eye view" in my daily life, but the inclusion of the word in the lyrics makes me feel that the word "bird's eye view" is quite familiar to me,
I don't want to continue to chase after the things in front of me,
I will try to think that it is right to look at things from a bird's eye view, rather than just chasing what is in front of me.
I really like this "look at things from a bird's eye view,
I understand.
I really feel like I received a letter from Tsunku III, or a message from him.
I feel like I got a letter from Tsunku III. The lyrics as a whole.
I like the part about looking down from a bird's eye view the best,
I think it gives me time to pause for a moment,
Yes, it does.
It's not a fast-paced world, after all.
There is a lot to think about and a lot to remember,
But I really like songs that make me stop and take a break.
I like the ending.
Right here.
"I'm sorry.
Really.
He said he's going to chew on it.
That's right. I love it so much.
The audition I went in for was titled "It's You Who Will Create Tomorrow,
I liked the message of the title,
I liked the message and auditioned for the song because I liked it,
It's just as you said earlier,
I felt as if I was receiving a message,
I hadn't listened to it recently,
I wanted to listen to it again,
I thought maybe if I listened to it one more time, I would remember how I felt when I auditioned,
I thought maybe if I listened to it again, I would remember how I felt when I auditioned.
I thought maybe if I listened to it one more time, I would remember how I felt when I auditioned.
I see, that was the title of your audition.
I think it certainly helps me to remember how I felt at the time,
When I listen to this song, it reminds me of the time when I was on tour right after I joined the band,
And this song, the chorus also says I love you, you, you,
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
It's a bit sad, but it's also a song I like to listen to quietly at night.
Please listen to this song when you want to take a moment to reflect on yourself.
Please look forward to the next episode!
Juice- Juice's Innovate and Angelem's Rin Hashizoko will be presenting the next episode of "Halo! Project for the next week.
Project's activities for the coming week in this new section, Halo Pro NEXT WEEK.
So, this time
Project's activities from August 1 to 7, the day after the distribution date.
Here it is.
Terrain.
O! There was a release,
Beth. Speaking of summer.
That's right.
It's full of Bess.
I'm so happy. Here.
Oh, there's Haru's photo album.
Oh, wow.
I've never talked with Haru.
I haven't either.
I've never talked to her either. Yes, you have.
I want to talk sometime.
I don't know, I have a lot on my mind. Yes, there are. But there are a lot of great release events in general, aren't there? That's right. It's a lot of release events,
What kind of time do you two have for each other? Well...
We can go to see each other in various places. That's right. We can go to places we normally can't go to, and the members of Juice in Osaka are amazing.
I think Juice has a lot of members in Osaka.
There were a lot of members from Osaka. I recently went to Osaka for Uemura-san's last single, so there were a lot of members in Osaka. So we always had delicious takoyaki every time we went.
Yume Kudo loves takoyaki, and I was really worried that she might get tired of them because she gets good takoyaki every time, and I was fighting the fear that I might not be able to get them anymore.
It was very Yume Kudo-like.
So you like takoyaki that much.
I guess so.
It's great because it makes them happy. That's why I'm so happy when the staff smiles and says they brought it. It's cute.
Yes, it is. I also recently held a release event for Ms. Sasaki's last single.
So I'm really looking forward to the reaction of the fans every time I perform. So I really look forward to the fans' reactions every time. It's certainly fresh, isn't it? They start to call out for the new song before you know it.
I thought, "Can you handle it already? I thought.
So fast! It's really wonderful. I just wanted to applaud them.
Hallo! Stage, right?
Also, there was a festival.
Tokyo Idol Festival 2024.
This time there are teams that will be on the 2nd, Beyonce and Rosie Chronicle, and Jui ce!Juice!Tsubaki Factory Ochanoma that will be on the 4th,
I love this festival called Tiff.
I love this festival called "Tiff". Why?
I have been participating in this festival since I was a trainee, and then I participated as a member of Kobushi and Juice, so I have been a part of this festival for a very long time.
I have been a part of JuiceJuice for a long time, but the first time I was invited to perform at Tokyo Idol Festival with JuiceJuice, I had to take a leave of absence.
So I was really disappointed. The year after that
So the following year, we were able to perform again! So we did. On the bus on the way back, I was smiling so much. I don't usually take pictures of Danbaralulu when she is off the bus, but she looked so happy that I took a picture of her.
But she looked so happy, so I told her to take a picture of me. She later sent it to me, and I realized how much she really loves me.
Is there anything you keep in mind at festivals?
What I try to keep in mind at festivals is that it's better to be fun and let the fun out in full force.
Juice has some cool songs, but rather than trying to be cool, there are a lot of things we have to do to make it better.
I have the image of Angstrom also performing at Rockin' every year, but are you conscious of that?
There are a lot of people who don't know Angstrom.
We all try to give a performance that will win the hearts of those who don't know us.
You look like you're having fun.
Even when I look back on it, it looks like fun, doesn't it?
Festivals are fun.
I'm having fun.
I look forward to working with you in the future!
Project Open Campus" is a new project.
It's a rare opportunity to dance with Mr. Mihashimaki, isn't it?
It's a rare opportunity, isn't it?
Hey...
It's not often that I get to meet him.
I don't see him very often these days, but I remember when we were practicing at the studio.
I was in the same studio with Maki-sensei, and I asked her a question about how I should dance here.
I got an answer that was different from what I was expecting, and I thought, "There is this kind of way of thinking.
I thought it was an open campus where I could learn a lot of things.
I travel all over the country, so it's hard for me to come to Tokyo.
I think it will be a good experience for those who can't come to Tokyo.
I hope it will be a good experience. I'm sure it will be a good experience. If you can make it, please come and spend time with Hello!
I might even be attending!
Oh Ah Ah Ah
I'm so excited, I'm so excited, I'm so excited
You're kind of lying, aren't you?
Just a little.
Surprise flag.
I'm just a little excited
Oh, Ah Ah
She doesn't even know I changed her nails or her hair.
Shut up and give me a compliment.
What's so cute about her?
All of it... Angry...
It's good to be in love.
If you go on to the next one... - No, no, no.
It's gonna be a pain in the ass.
The Link Between Life and Death
Yes, I can
Matching Idiots!
I really admire you so much
I don't have one.
I'm standing on a thing, and you say it's a kiss
That's why it's so ambiguous
I don't need more than a few lines...
His disappearing act...
I don't pretend to have it all figured out
I want your love, love, love
I want you so much
So give me my love
You want to dream, don't you?
Love Love Love
Gimme Gimme Gimme Gimme Your Love
If you sing
Love Love Love
You'll be my love
Yay!
Someone else will see my love
I'll be able to see it all straight
I want this and that
Forgive me for wasting my time
I don't have it. I don't have it.
I'm standing on a thing, and you say it's a kiss
So vague
I don't want more than a few vague lines
He's gone, he's gone.
I don't pretend to have it all figured out
I want your love, love, love
I want you so much
So give me my love
You want to dream, don't you?
Love Love Love
Gimme Gimme Your Love
Gimme My Love
Gimme your love
Love Love Love
Gimme Gimme Gimme Your Love
Gimme My Love
You're doing your best every day.
This is Halo! Sta. of JuiceJuice and Rin Hajime of Angelem.
It's almost time to say goodbye.
It's a rare chance to talk to you, Rin.
When you're up and at 'angsty'...
That language-less intertwining... on stage and off stage.
It's not often that we get to intertwine on stage.
We didn't expect the timing to be so perfect, and I was staring at Rin-chan the whole time.
She was looking at me quite closely, and she even made a funny face to tell me that she was okay.
It was the first time I had talked to her since then, so I was looking forward to seeing how it would turn out.
So I'm glad you had a good time. I had a good time too.
I'm glad you had a good time and I had a good time too.
Hello Project 2024 Summer All of Us Vega Altair is now underway!
This weekend, we'll be performing in Hiroshima.
Hiroshima.
It's my hometown.
Oh!
That's right, they might give us some rice-bran paste.
And on August 4th, JuiceJuice Tsubaki Factory Ochanoma will be performing at Tokyo Idol Festival 2024!
Well, you know, there's a lot of moving around in this festival, so please bring your water and towels for the goodies.
So if you bring water and a towel, you can enjoy the festival and take good care of yourself.
And on August 12, Angulum and Ju ice Juice will perform at the Rockin' Japan Festival 2024!
I'm so glad. They'll be on the same stage on the same day.
I'm looking forward to seeing you on the staff stage.
I'll be waiting for you. Project will be uploading new videos every Wednesday.
We'll be uploading a new video every Wednesday, so please leave us a comment!
Please subscribe to our channel! This time I'm joined by Rei Inoue of JuiceJuice and Rin Yatsugi of Angulum.
Good bye.